Lorenzo Johnston Greene Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Academic File, 1680-1990 (Box 7-65)
  - Administrative File, 1925-1988 (Box 7-24)
    - Institute to Facilitate Desegregation in Kansas City, Mo. Public Schools
      - Grant proposals and related material, 1970-1974, undated, (3 folders)
      - Letters of thanks to Kansas City, Mo., school officials, 1973
      - Memoranda, 1973-1974, undated
      - Miscellaneous, 1973-1974, undated
      - Reports, studies, and related material, 1973-1974, undated (Box 17)
    - Meetings
      - 1934-1970, undated, (5 folders)
      - 1971-1987, undated (Box 18)
    - Memoranda
      - 1941-1969, (5 folders)
      - 1970-1981, (7 folders) (Box 19)
      - 1982-1987, undated, (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - Reports and studies re Lincoln University
      - 1934-1987, (4 folders)
      - Undated (Box 21)
    - Students
      - Alumni, 1946, 1963-1986, undated
        - Miscellaneous, 1946, 1963-1986, undated
        - Smith, Frederick E., 1981, undated
      - Course critiques, undated
      - Directories and lists, 1925-1972, undated
      - Letters of recommendation, 1942-1986, undated, (2 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1936, 1971, undated
      - Veterans, 1942-1946, undated
    - Surveys and questionnaires, undated (Box 22)
    - University placement services, 1970-1973, undated, (2 folders)
    - Vitae and applications for academic employment
      - "A-Do" miscellaneous, 1946-1984, undated, (3 folders)
      - "Dr-N" miscellaneous, 1966-1973, undated, (5 folders) (Box 23)
      - "P-Z" miscellaneous, 1933-circa 1986, undated, (4 folders) (Box 24)
  - Correspondence, 1928-1988 (Box 24-36)
    Correspondence sent and received with attached and related material.
    Arranged alphabetically by name of person or organization.
    - "A" miscellaneous, 1933-1987, undated, (3 folders) (Box 24)
    - Bethel, Elizabeth R., 1981-1987 (Box 25)
    - Bonner, Cynthia B., 1942-1963, undated
    - Brigham, Robert I., 1943-1973, undated, (3 folders)
    - "Ba-Bl" miscellaneous, 1934-1986, undated, (4 folders)
    - "Br-By" miscellaneous, 1934-1987, undated, (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - Chapman, Oscar J., 1960-1973, undated, (3 folders)
    - "Ca-Cl" miscellaneous, 1933-1986, undated, (2 folders)
    - "Co-Cz" miscellaneous, 1934-1986, undated, (3 folders) (Box 27)
    - Daniel, Walter C., 1969-1978, undated
    - Dawson, Earl E., 1939-1969
    - "D" miscellaneous, 1933-1985, undated, (3 folders)
    - Eichhorst, Thomas E., 1963-1977 (Box 28)
    - "E-Gi" miscellaneous, 1928-1987, undated, (6 folders)
    - "Gj-Gu" miscellaneous, 1934-1985, undated, (2 folders) (Box 29)
    - Hudson, Gossie, 1972-1974, undated
    - "H" miscellaneous, 1933-1987, undated, (4 folders)
    - "I-J" miscellaneous, 1938-1987, undated, (3 folders) (Box 30)
    - Kremer, Gary R., 1970-1985, undated
    - "K-L" miscellaneous, 1934-1987, undated, (4 folders)
    - Macmillan Co., 1933-1971, undated (Box 31)
    - Marshall, Albert P., 1962-1986
    - McGraw Hill Book Co., 1933-1944, 1968
    - Meier, August, 1963-1974, 1981-1985, undated
    - Miller, James Erroll, 1939-1971, undated
    - Mountain, Elsie M., 1935-1944
    - "Ma-McG" miscellaneous, 1934-1986, undated, (3 folders)
    - "McH-N" miscellaneous, 1934-1987, undated, (5 folders) (Box 32)
    - Oak, Vishnu V., 1943-1948
    - "O" miscellaneous, 1942-1972
    - Pride, Armistead S., 1949, 1964-1972
    - "Pac-Par" miscellaneous, 1938-1986, undated
    - "Pat-Q" miscellaneous, 1933-1986, undated, (4 folders) (Box 33)
    - Reddick, Lawrence D., 1934-1982
    - Reid, Ira De A., 1943-1946
    - Robinson, W. Stitt, 1968-1982
    - "R" miscellaneous, 1934-1987, undated, (4 folders)
    - Savage, W. Sherman, 1933-1967 (Box 34)
    - Scruggs, Sherman D., 1938-1953
    - Stamper, Cletus, 1967-1986
    - "Sa-Ss" miscellaneous, 1934-1988, undated, (6 folders)
    - "St-Wa" miscellaneous, 1934-1987, undated, (8 folders) (Box 35)
    - "We-Z" miscellaneous, 1934-1988, undated, (5 folders) (Box 36)
    - Unidentified, 1934-1987, undated
  - General, 1929-1990 (Box 36-47)
    Correspondence, bibliographies, fliers, reports, newsletters, newspapers, news releases, clippings, publishers' catalogs and brochures, student writings, yearbooks, printed matter, and miscellaneous material.
    Organized alphabetically by name of organization, activity, subject, person, or type of material.
    - Advisory Committee on Training for Colored Social Workers, 1929-1930 (Box 36)
    - Albert A. Kildare Memorial Fund, 1960-1968, undated
    - Anderson, Marian, 1939, undated
    - Annie Malone Children's Home, St. Louis, Mo., 1979-1984, undated
    - Bibliographies and book lists, 1934, 1938, 1945-1985, undated, (5 folders) (Box 37)
    - "The Black Frontier" film project
      - Correspondence, 1969-1970
      - Miscellaneous, 1968-1970, undated
    - Book and Pen Club, 1955-1958, 1965, undated
    - Civilian Defense Corps, 1942, undated (Box 38)
    - Clippings, 1940-1990, undated
    - Columbia University, New York, N.Y., 1934-1987, undated
    - Course examinations and problems, 1940-1970, 1980, undated
    - Dr. Lorenzo Johnston Greene Day, 1973
    - Ethnic Studies Center, 1980-1986, undated
    - Fabio, Sarah W., Saga of the Black Man (drama), 1968
    - Historical societies and museums
      - Miscellaneous, 1946, 1959-1986, undated
      - Old Derby Historical Society, Derby, Conn., 1981-1988, undated
      - Parting Ways Museum of Afro-American Ethnohistory, Plymouth, Mass.
        - Anderson, Marjorie E., director, 1980-1986, undated
        - National Endowment for the Humanities Summer Seminar for high school teachers, 1983-1984 (Box 39)
        - Parting Ways settlement, 1977-1981
        - Pearse, Abraham, 1981-1983, undated
        - Planning colloquium, 1977
        - Search Committee, 1984-1985
        - Transition from Slavery to Freedom in Plymouth and Southeastern Massachusetts project
          - "Conditions of & Responses to Slavery in Plymouth, 1680 to the Revolution" and related material, n.d
          - Correspondence and memoranda, 1981-1984
          - Miscellaneous, 1981-1984, undated
          - Reports
            - Miscellaneous, 1981-1984, undated
            - Monthly, 1981-1982
        - Users manual for Parting Ways research facilities, 1982
      - Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C., 1981-1987, undated
    - Honorary degree, University of Missouri, Columbia, Mo., 1971 (Box 40)
    - Howard University, Washington, D. C., 1932, 1963, undated
    - Integration of the Afro-American Folk Arts through Music project, Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., 1976-1983
    - Intercultural education, 1940, 1944
    - Kappa Alpha Psi fraternity, 1934-1986, undated, (2 folders)
    - Lincoln University luminaries, biographical material, 1972-1988
    - Midwest Committee on Discrimination in Higher Education, 1952-1955, undated
    - Missouri sharecroppers roadside demonstrations (1939-1940)
      - Delmo Housing Corporation, 1954-1979, undated
      - Documentary film projects, 1984-1987, undated, (2 folders) (Box 41)
      - General correspondence, 1939-1940, 1984-1986, undated
      - Johnson, Walter and Cecil (father and son), 1939
      - Miscellaneous, 1938-1939, 1981-1985, undated
      - Mitchell, Harry L.
        - Biographical material, 1979, 1986-1987
        - Correspondence, 1980-1987, undated
      - Narratives and background material, 1987, undated
      - Sharecroppers correspondence, 1939, undated
      - Southwest Missouri Farm Resettlement Project, Farm Security Administration, 1939-1940, n.d
    - Missouri State Committee on the Negro Emancipation Centennial, 1961-1963
    - Missouri State Conference on the Employment Problems of the Negro, 1939, undated (Box 42)
    - NAACP, 1941-1985, undated
    - Negro History Week, 1935-1969, 1982, undated
    - News releases, 1970-1983, undated
    - Newsletters, newspapers, and related material
      - American Outpost, London, England, 1944
      - In Fact, New York, N.Y., 1942, 1944-1946
      - Miscellaneous, 1938-1985, undated
      - Southern Patriot, Nashville, Tenn., 1945
    - Publishers' announcements, brochures and catalogs
      - 1935-1968
      - 1969-1985, undated, (5 folders) (Box 43)
    - Retirement correspondence, 1969-1973, undated (Box 44)
    - Seaforth Junior Secondary School, St. Thomas, Jamaica, Cynthia Bolt Bonner, principal, 1973-1984, undated
    - Student writings
      - Afro-American studies
        - 1929, 1944, 1960-1972, (3 folders)
        - 1973-1977, undated, (4 folders) (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous
        - 1935-1939, 1956-1965, (3 folders)
        - 1966-1970, undated, (5 folders) (Box 46)
      - Missouri history
        - 1965, 1971
      - Undated (Box 47)
    - Tennessee A. & I. State College, Nashville, Tenn., 1943-1944, undated
    - Tennessee Folklore Society, 1955-1957
    - Yearbooks, 1957, 1965, 1967, (3 folders)
  - Midwest Journal, 1945-1973 (Box 48-60)
    Correspondence, manuscript articles, short stories, poems, transcriptions of archival documents, biographical material, galleys, subscription and circulation lists, brochures, and miscellaneous material. Later material relates to reprint permissions and microfilming projects.
    Arranged into administrative, correspondence with publishers, editorial, general correspondence, and Lincoln University Research Journal (predecessor of the Midwest Journal ) files.
    - Administrative file (Box 48)
      - Circulation and subscription material, 1949-1956, undated
      - Gallagher, Norman B. (owner of Tri-County Publications), 1952-1956, undated, (2 folders)
      - Inter-City Press, 1950-1951, undated
      - Library of Congress, 1949-1957, undated
      - Mid-State Printing Co., 1949-1956, undated
      - Miscellaneous, 1949-1956, undated
    - Correspondence with publishers
      - Alfred A. Knopf, 1948-1955, undated
      - "A-B" miscellaneous, 1948-1973, undated, (2 folders)
      - Columbia University Press, 1948-1956, undated
      - "C-G" miscellaneous, 1948-1955, undated, (2 folders) (Box 49)
      - Harcourt, Brace and Co., 1948-1955, undated
      - Harper and Brothers, 1948-1956, undated
      - "H-J " miscellaneous, 1948-1955, undated, (2 folders)
      - Little, Brown and Co., 1948-1955, undated
      - "L" miscellaneous, 1949-1961, undated
      - Macmillan Co., 1948-1957, undated
      - McGraw Hill, 1949-1952, undated
      - Microfilming Corporation of America, 1970-1971, undated
      - "M-N" miscellaneous, 1951-1956, undated
      - Oxford University Press, 1948-1955, undated
      - "O" miscellaneous, 1955
      - Prentice Hall, 1948-1956
      - Princeton University Press, 1949-1956, undated (Box 50)
      - "P-T" miscellaneous, 1948-1955, undated, (3 folders)
      - University of North Carolina Press, 1954-1955, undated
      - University of Oklahoma Press, 1950-1956, undated
      - "U-V" miscellaneous, 1948-1956, undated
      - Westminster Press, 1952-1956
      - "W-Y" miscellaneous, 1949-1955, undated
    - Editorial file
      - Biographical sketches of contributors, 1949, undated
      - Editorial board and editorial staff, 1946-1953, undated
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1956, undated
      - Publishers brochures and publicity material, 1950-1955, undated, (2 folders)
      - Review books tracking sheets, undated (Box 51)
      - Text copy
        - Index, vols. 1-6, 1948-1955, (2 folders)
        - Vols. 1-2, 1948-1950
        - Vol. 4, 1952
        - Vols. 5-6, 1952-1954, (5 folders) (Box 52)
        - Vol. 6, 1954, (6 folders) (Box 53)
        - Vol. 7, 1955-1956, (7 folders) (Box 54)
        - Anonymous and fragmentary works, 1949, undated
        - Miscellaneous articles, documents, folktales, and poems, 1948-1956, undated (Box 55)
    - General correspondence
      - "A" miscellaneous, 1948-1958, undated
      - British Information Service, 1948-1952, undated
      - "Ba-Br" miscellaneous, 1948-1973, undated, (3 folders)
      - "Bu-E" miscellaneous, 1948-1973, undated, (7 folders) (Box 56)
      - Filler, Louis, 1950-1956, undated
      - Fischel, Leslie H., 1949-1955
      - Fiszman, Joseph R., 1955-1956
      - Flechtheim, Ossip K. and Lili, 1949-1955
      - Fletcher, T. Thomas Fortune, 1948-1957, undated
      - "F" miscellaneous, 1948-1956 (Box 57)
      - Griffin, William J., 1949-1955, undated
      - "G" miscellaneous, 1948-1963, undated, (2 folders)
      - Hamilton, Horace E., 1950-1956, undated
      - Hammond, Harold E., 1952-1955, undated
      - Hansberry, William Leo, 1955, undated
      - Heckscher, Kay, 1952-1955, undated
      - Herkovits, Melville J., 1949-1956
      - Hughes, Langston, 1949-1955
      - "H" miscellaneous, 1948-1955, undated, (2 folders)
      - Ikemoto, Takashi, 1952-1954
      - "J" miscellaneous, 1948-1954, undated
      - "K" miscellaneous, 1948-1954, undated (Box 58)
      - Lee, Ulysses Y., 1949-1955, undated
      - "L" miscellaneous, 1948-1956
      - Meier, August, 1951-1956, undated
      - "M-O" miscellaneous, 1948-1955, undated, (4 folders)
      - Polin, Raymond, 1953-1956, undated
      - des Pres, Francois M. T., 1949-1956, undated
      - "P" miscellaneous, 1948-1954
      - Quarles, Benjamin, 1948-1956, undated
      - Reddick, Lawrence D., 1949-1955, n .d.
      - "R" miscellaneous, 1949-1963, undated (Box 59)
      - Sakata, Taro, 1952-1953
      - Scott, Nathan A., 1953-1955, undated
      - Scruggs, Sherman D., 1949-1955, undated
      - Segy, Ladislas, 1951-1956, undated
      - Shepperson, George, 1952-1953
      - Smythe, Hugh H. and Mabel M., 1948-1956, undated
      - Starr, Richard F., 1955-1956, undated
      - "S" miscellaneous, 1948-1963, undated, (2 folders)
      - Talbot, Walter R., 1955-1956, undated
      - "T-U" miscellaneous, 1948-1957, undated
      - Van Horn, Ruth G., 1952-1956, undated (Box 60)
      - "V" miscellaneous, 1953-1955
      - Williamson, Hugh P., 1949-1956, undated
      - Winslow, Henry F., 1951-1955, undated
      - Woodress, James, 1955-1956, undated
      - "W-Z" miscellaneous, 1948-1961, undated, (2 folders)
      - Unidentified, 1948, undated
    - Lincoln University Research Journal (predecessor of Midwest Journal )
      - Correspondence, "A-Y" miscellaneous, 1946-1947, undated, (3 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1945-1948, undated
  - Research File, 1680-1987 (Box 61-65)
    Reports, correspondence, topical files, photostats of archival documents, draft books, statistical material, legal documents, and miscellaneous material.
    Arranged alphabetically by name of organization, person, subject, activity, or type of material.
    - Afro-American colleges (Box 61)
      - Lists, undated
      - Theater education, 1968
    - Afro-Americans
      - Businesses, 1933-1957, undated
      - Connecticut, 1680-1762, 1774-1792, 1803, 1963, undated, (2 folders)
      - Massachusetts
        - Jennison v. Walker and the extinction of slavery in Massachusetts, 1688-1788, 1947, 1983, undated
        - Miscellaneous, 1688-1788, 1947, undated
      - Minnesota, 1945, 1947 (Box 62)
      - Missouri
        - Beasley, Edward and Enid Mushkin, "An Outline History of Blacks in Kansas City 1800-1978," 1979
        - Clamorgan, Cyprian. The Colored Aristocracy of St. Louis. St. Louis, Mo., 1858
        - Marriage record project, 1972, undated
        - Military units
          - Sixty-fifth and Sixty-eighth regiments, United States Colored Troops, lists and data sheets
          - Third Missouri Heavy Artillery regiment, muster roll fragments, 1863 See Oversize
          - Unidentified muster roll fragments, 1865 See also Oversize
        - Miscellaneous, 1963-1970, undated
        - "Odyssey of the Columbia Black Community Since Emancipation," 1981
        - Patterson, Dilcey Ann (former slave) interview, 1936
        - Public schools
          - Miscellaneous, 1929-1974, undated
          - Sumner High School, St. Louis, Mo., 1987
        - Stauffer, Grant, "The Free Negro in Missouri, 1850-1860," master's thesis research material (including photo reproduction of Bruce, H.C., The New Man, Twenty-Nine Years a Slave. Twenty-Nine Years a Free Man, York, Pa., 1895), 1895, 1972, (2 folders) (Box 63)
        - Young, William H. and Nathan B., Your Kansas City and Mine, 1950
      - Professors
        - Attendance at professional meetings, 1937-1954, undated
        - Pay equalization, 1935-1948, undated
      - Rhode Island
        - First Rhode Island Regiment, 1778-1779
        - Slaves, 1781-1786, 1880, 1946
        - "Statement of Invalid Accounts" and other material re veterans of Revolutionary War, 1790, 1945-1946, undated
      - Sports Since 1947 project, 1966
      - Textbooks, 1961-1969, undated See also Oversize
      - Utah and the Mormon Church, 1969, 1978-1979, undated
      - World War II
        - American Teachers Association. The Black and White of Rejections for Military Service, (Montgomery, Ala., 1944)
        - Military units, undated (Box 64)
        - War industries
          - Miscellaneous, 1940-1941
          - Office of Production Management, 1940-1942, undated
    - Aging study, 1959
    - Archival material on Afro-Americans
      - Correspondence, Alabama-Washington, D.C., 1934-1983, (2 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1791, 1815, 1843, 1944, 1967, 1973
    - Black v. Missouri, 1982
    - British Information Service, 1943, 1948-1957, 1970
    - Bush, George W. and William O., Afro-American pioneers in the Pacific Northwest, 1954
    - Clements v. Teaford, 1967-1970, undated
    - Czechoslovak National Council of America, 1943-1944
    - Downing, George, Afro-American abolitionist, undated
    - Fairground Park incident, St. Louis, Mo., 1949
    - Indians and Mexicans in Minnesota, 1947-1948
    - Lincoln University history, 1936, 1961-1981, 1985, undated (Box 65)
    - Miscellaneous publications, 1939-1972, 1982, undated
    - Missouri military units, Civil War, First World War, and Korean War eras, 1952, 1964, undated
    - Segregation and desegregation, 1954-1956
    - United States Bureau of the Census
      - Census of agriculture, summary by states and special reports re Missouri, 1935
      - Census of housing for St. Louis, Mo., 1980
      - Crop and livestock summaries, 1935
      - Farm acreage and value reports, 1935
      - Farm and census preliminary reports re Missouri counties, 1935
      - Miscellaneous, undated
      - Releases, 1933-1935
      - Social and economic characteristics by race report for Missouri for 1970 and 1980, undated
- Professional Organizations, 1933-1988 (Box 66-76)
  Correspondence, minutes, reports, proposals, constitutions, financial statements, printed matter, and miscellaneous material.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of organization, subject, activity, and type of material.
  - American Association of University Professors, 1942-1969, undated (Box 66)
  - American Management Association, 1968, undated
  - Association for the Study of Afro-American Life and History (ASALH)
    - Annual meetings
      - 1975-1981
      - 1982-1987, (6 folders) (Box 67)
    - Associated Publishers
      - Afro-American History Kit series, 1982-1985
      - Correspondence, 1981-1987 (Box 68)
      - Journal of Negro History
        - Correspondence, 1974-1986
        - Miscellaneous, 1981-1986, undated
        - Reports, 1978-1984
      - Miscellaneous, 1979-1986, undated
    - Constitutions and related material, 1973-1985, undated
    - Executive Council
      - Banks v. Association for the Study of Afro-American Life and History, Inc., 1985
      - Correspondence, 1979-1987, undated
      - Employee packet, 1980
      - Meetings, 1976-1985 (Box 69)
      - Miscellaneous, 1983-1984, undated
      - Reports, 1975-1988, undated
    - Financial statements, 1979-1987, undated
    - General correspondence
      - "A" miscellaneous, 1982-1984
      - Banks, Samuel L., 1983-1985
      - "B-F" miscellaneous, 1974-1986, (4 folders)
      - Gillespie, Bonnie J., 1984-1986
      - "G" miscellaneous, 1980-1985, undated
      - Hornsby, Alton, Jr., 1977-1987, undated (Box 70)
      - "H-M" miscellaneous, 1973-1987, (4 folders)
      - Picott, J. Rupert, 1973-1984, undated
      - "P-W" miscellaneous, 1973-1987, undated, (4 folders)
      - Unidentified, 1983-1985, undated
    - Historical and biographical material, including data re ASNLH, 1987, undated
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1987, undated
    - Program proposals, 1981-1982, undated
  - Association for the Study of Negro Life and History (ASNLH)
    - Annual meetings
      - 1943-1952
      - 1954 (Box 71)
      - 1955
        - Correspondence
        - Miscellaneous
      - 1956-1957, (2 folders)
      - 1959-1963
      - 1964
        - Correspondence
        - Miscellaneous
      - 1965-1970, (2 folders) (Box 72)
    - Associated Publishers, 1942-1972, undated
    - Constitutions, 1950-1965, undated
    - Executive Council, 1951-1971, undated
    - Fund-raising and financial statements, 1949-1961, undated
    - General correspondence
      - "A" miscellaneous, 1954-1968, undated
      - Brewer, William M., 1950-1968, undated
      - "B-H" miscellaneous, 1937-1972, undated, (5 folders) (Box 73)
      - Jackson, Harvey, 1952-1965
      - "J-K" miscellaneous, 1941-1967, undated73
      - Logan, Rayford W., 1936-1952, undated
      - "L-Q" miscellaneous, 1945-1973, undated, (3 folders)
      - Reddick, Lawrence D., 1950-1968
      - "R" miscellaneous, 1951-1973, undated (Box 74)
      - Segy, Ladislaw, 1952-1956, undated
      - "S-V" miscellaneous, 1937-1972, undated
      - Wesley, Charles H., 1937-1966, undated, (2 folders)
      - Wesley, Charles H. and Dorothy P., 1967-1986, undated
      - Woodson, Carter G.
        - 1933-1939, undated
        - 1940-1949, undated (Box 75)
      - "W" miscellaneous, 1945-1965, undated
      - Unidentified, 1951-1965
    - Woodson, Carter G.
      - Correspondence and other material re essays in honor of Woodson, 1940, undated
      - Writings by Woodson, 1936, undated
  - Association of Social Science Teachers
    - Association of Social Science Teachers in Negro Schools (predecessor organization), 1944-1951, undated
    - Miscellaneous, 1950-1970, undated
  - Mid-Missouri Council for the Social Sciences, 1938-1958, undated
  - Miscellaneous, 1970-1983, undated
  - Missouri Council on Historic Preservation, 1973-1974, undated, (2 folders)
  - Missouri Historical Records Advisory Board
    - Correspondence, 1983-1987, undated
    - Miscellaneous, 1983-1987, undated, (2 folders) (Box 76)
  - Missouri State Association of Negro Teachers, 1938-1945, undated
  - Missouri State Library Coordinating Board for Higher Education, 1986-1987, undated
  - Missouri State Teachers Association, 1939-1983
  - Southern Association of Africanists, 1974
- Public Interest Organizations, 1931-1988 (Box 76-91)
  Correspondence, minutes, plans, newsletters, press releases, reports, statements, membership lists, clippings, draft legislation, directories, printed matter, and miscellaneous material.
  Organized alphabetically by name of organizations.
  - A. Philip Randolph Institute, 1965, 1980, undated (Box 76)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1953-1980, undated
  - American Foundation for Negro Affairs, 1968, undated
  - American Management Association, 1968-1970, undated
  - Committee on Residential Standards, Jefferson City, Mo., 1966, undated (Box 77)
  - Congress of Racial Equality, 1953
  - Episcopal Church, Diocese of Missouri
    - Grace Episcopal Church, 1957-1985, undated
    - Mintz, Arnold E., 1962-1974, undated
    - Miscellaneous, 1959-1974, undated
  - Governor's Advisory Council on Aging, Missouri, 1966-1981
  - Jefferson City Council on Religion and Race, Jefferson City, Mo., 1967, undated
  - Jewish organizations, 1958-1983, undated
  - Kiwanis Club, 1974-1987, undated
  - Mayor's Senior Citizens Advisory Commission, Jefferson City, Mo., 1961-1984, undated